Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records and Drawings Collection PR 53
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- City College of New York - New York, NY
  - Gymnasium - entrance floor plan; diazotype on paper, 1904-12-13 (Box 227-B)
  - Gymnasium - main floor plan; diazotype on paper, 1904-12-13 (Box 227-B)
  - Gymnasium - details; diazotype on paper (damaged), 1904-12-13 (Box 227-B)
  - Gymnasium - details of construction of running track; diazotype & blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box 227-B)
  - Mechanical Arts Building - re-arrangement of exhaust & vapor pipes; diazotype on linen, 1905-11-9 (Box 227-B)
  - Gymnasium - structural details; diazotype on linen, 1904-12-13 (Box 227-B)
  - Gymnasium - details of cast-iron door frames & partitions from stairs; blueprint on paper (damaged), 1905-1-9 (Box 255-B)
  - Gymnasium - strain diagrams; blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box 255-B)
  - Gymnasium - openings & doors, lintels & bucks; blueprint on paper, 1905-1-9 (Box 255-B)
  - Mechanical Arts Building - openings for ventilating ducts & steam pipes through engine & dynamo foundations; blueprint on paper (Box 255-B)
  - Mechanical Arts Building - location of vacuum machinery; blueprint on paper, 1906-3-12 (Box 255-B)
  - Mechanical Arts Building - boiler room details [?]; blueprint on paper (Box 255-B)
  - Gymnasium - framing: details & schedules; ink on paper (25 sheets), 1904-3-14 (Box 255-B)
  - Chemical Building - framing: details of columns; ink on linen (34 sheets), 1905 (Box 255-B)
  - Main Building - marble bases to door trims to toilet rooms with double door from main corridor; graphite on trace, 1905-11-15 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - location of basins, students' toilet basement; graphite on trace, 1905-08-10 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - plaster beams & cornices, gallery & ceiling, museum of natural history, 3rd fl.; graphite on trace (Box 368)
  - Main Building - rafter cut & placed to escape mechanism for darkening shades, 3rd fl.; graphite on trace (Box 368)
  - Main Building - cement asphalt floor in hat & coat room & lunch room, ground fl.; graphite on trace, 1906-07-24 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - jointing marble stair platforms, north & south towers; graphite on trace (damaged), 1906-08-16 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - assembly hall, detail of column bases, etc.; graphite on trace (Box 368)
  - Main Building - splayed plaster jamb & head, tracery windows in assembly hall; graphite on trace, 1906-05-12 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - cleat supports at top of pendulum shaft; graphite on trace, 1906-06-20 (Box 368)
  - All buildings - detail of drop on typical newel; graphite on trace, 1904-12-14 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - marble plinth in corridor to rm 2, 6th fl.; graphite on trace, 1906-09-14 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - tile wainscot in living plant room, dept. of natural history; graphite on trace, 1906-03-29 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - half elevation of truss in assembly hall; graphite on trace, 1906-09-05 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - setting [...?], assembly hall; graphite on trace (damaged), 1906-09-26 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - transom in hat & coat room; graphite on trace (damaged), 1905-10-03 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - ridge roll, apex of assembly hall roof; graphite on trace, 1906-03-30 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - top of plaster caps under roof trusses in assembly hall; graphite on trace, 1906-09-20 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - entrance door details, wing A & E; graphite on trace, 1906-02-16 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - assembly hall, detail of super caps on tracery caps etc.; graphite on trace (Box 368)
  - Main Building - half plan of corridor C, marble floor; graphite on trace, 1905-12-26 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - marble floor tiling, exhibition hall & lobby; graphite on trace (damaged), 1906-07-31 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - assembly hall, angle iron & metal lath furring to columns, etc.; graphite on trace, 1906-06-05 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - assembly hall, angle iron & metal lath furring to columns, etc.; graphite on trace (damaged), 1906-06-05 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - interior details of main tower ground floor; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - assembly hall, angle iron furrings, etc.; graphite on trace, 1906-06-27 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - assembly hall, angle iron & metal lath furring to pilasters; graphite on trace, 1906-05-28 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - details of room for casts; graphite on trace (Box 368)
  - Main Building - flooring around piers in lab #1, ground fl.; graphite on trace, 1906-04-12 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - detail of finish of plaster jambs, wing C; graphite on trace, 1906-08-10 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - omissions of tile in lunch room, ground fl.; graphite on trace, 1906-12-06 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - assembly hall, opening to plaster arches under gallery; ink on linen, 1905-12-20 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - portion of skewback removed to make space for terra cotta; graphite on trace (damaged), 1905-10-26 (Box 368)
  - All buildings - recitation room clock; graphite on trace, 1905-07-05 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - detail of galvanized iron work of truss in roof, assembly hall; graphite on trace (damaged, 2 pieces), 1906-09-05 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - changes in overhead work for reading room elevator; ink on linen, 1906-09-19 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - masonry openings, main corridor; graphite on trace, 1905-04-29 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - masonry openings, main corridor; ink on linen (damaged), 1905-08-29 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - new position of grilles in front of radiators, room #2, 1st floor, wing A; graphite on trace, 1906-09-13 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - toilets in basement; graphite on trace, 1905-10-06 (Box 368)
  - All building - master clock dial; ink on linen (Box 368)
  - All buildings - detail of thresholds; graphite on trace, 1905-02-28 (Box 368)
  - All buildings - details of all newels & handrails; graphite on trace, 1904-11-29 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - advance sheet showing altered plan of reading room, etc.; ink on linen, 1904-07-27 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - location of cutout boxes, 1st fl.; graphite on trace, 1905-10-23 (Box 368)
  - All buildings - detail of hose rack; graphite on trace, 1905-09-30 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - clock face for auditorium; graphite on trace (damaged), 1905-09-30 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - detail of small window in dark room; graphite on trace, 1905-06-23 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - distribution boxes & doors; graphite on trace, 1905-08-24 (Box 368)
  - All buildings - bracket for wood hand rail at stairs; graphite on trace (damaged), 1905-03-16 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - stack room interconnection box; graphite on trace, 1906-07-19 (Box 368)
  - All buildings - glass tile cap at intersection of glass tile wall & plaster ceiling; graphite on trace, 1905-07-01 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - plan of plaster piers in exhibition hall; graphite on trace, 1906-04-03 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - connection at wordwork & iron partition, 5th floor; graphite on trace, 1906-08-13 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - 1st floor plan, framing alterations; ink on linen, 1904-09-27 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - assembly hall, setting plan of corbels of museum; graphite on trace, 1906-09-26 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - rearrangement of partitions, 2nd fl.; graphite on trace, 1906-07-18 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - plan of dark room in lab., 3rd fl.; graphite on trace, 1905-05-24 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - part plan of reading room; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - corbels in corridors under assembly hall gallery cantilevers; graphite on trace, 1906-10-26 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - section on center line of main tower; graphite on trace, 1904-10-26 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - support of gadles[?] for house tank; ink on linen, 1905-01-20 (Box 368)
  - Main Building - erection diagram for main roof & janitor's 2nd fl. plan; ink on linen, 1905-07-21 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - C tier beams section C; ink on linen, 1905-03-03 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - B tier beams, section C; ink on linen, 1904-09-19 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - 2nd floor plan, D tier beams section C; ink on linen, 1904-11-05 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - 3rd floor plan, E tier beams section C; ink on linen, 1904-11-18 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - 4th floor plan, F tier beams section C; ink on linen, 1904-11-12 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - 5th floor plan, G tier beams section C; ink on linen, 1905-04-07 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - 6th floor plan, H tier beams section C; ink on linen, 1905-04-22 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - assembly hall, roof purlin plan; ink on linen, 1905-02-09 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - column setting plan & A tier beams; ink on linen (damaged), 1904-08-16 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - turret framing; ink on linen, 1905-09-27 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - K & L tier beams section C; ink on linen, 1905-05-01 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - column schedule; ink on linen, 1904-08-10 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - end frame truss T1; ink on linen, 1905-01-25 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - arched truss sect. C; ink on linen, 1905-01-16 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - parabolic sounding board; ink on linen, 1904-12-06 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - roof girders, sections AB & DE; ink on linen, 1905-01-28 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - roof purlin plan, panels C r/l sections AB & DE; ink on linen, 1905-01-27 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - roof purlin plan panels A & B, sectio, AB; ink on linen, 1905-01-27 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - roof purlin plan, panels J & K, section DE; ink on linen, 1905-01-27 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - roof purlin plan: panels D, E, H, G; ink on linen, 1905-01-28 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - roof purlin plan: panels F, I; ink on linen, 1905-04-12 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - roof purlin plan, panels N & T; ink on linen, 1905-04-14 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - roof purlin plan: panels P, Q, V, W; ink on linen, 1905-04-10 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - girders, F tier 4th fl.; ink on linen, 1905-03-03 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - framing for passageway btwn small towers; ink on linen, 1905-03-09 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - 5th floor, G tier girders; ink on linen, 1905-04-20 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - trusses; ink on linen, 1905-03-28 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - girders, 6th fl.; ink on linen, 1905-04-20 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - purlin plan, apse roof; ink on linen, 1905-04-28 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - framing above spring line proscenium arch; ink on linen, 1906-06-22 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - trusses, section C; ink on linen, 1904-12-21 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - column setting plan, sections AB & DE; ink on linen, 1904-08-15 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - B tier, ground floor plan section A-B; ink on linen, 1904-08-27 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - B tier ground floor plan, section DE; ink on linen, 1904-08-27 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - C tier floor plan, section AB; ink on linen, 1904-09-31 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - C tier floor plan, section D-E; ink on linen, 1904-09-30 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - BM tier or mezzanine, sec. C; ink on linen, 1904-10-11 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - D tier, 2nd fl. plan section AB; ink on linen, 1904-10-31 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - D tier 2nd fl. plan, section DE; ink on linen, 1904-10-31 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - E tier 3rd fl., section AB; ink on linen, 1904-11-18 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - E tier 3rd fl., section DE; ink on linen, 1904-11-18 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - F tier 4th fl., section AB; ink on linen, 1905-03-03 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - F tier 4th fl., section DE; ink on linen, 1905-03-02 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - roof plan, section AB; ink on linen, 1905-05-07 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - roof plan (framing), section D-E; ink on linen, 1905-05-07 (Box 368-A)
  - Main Building - raised floor framing C & E tiers; ink on linen, 1904-09-30 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - girders EG-3,4,5, section C; ink on linen, 1904-11-09 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - D & E tier girders; ink on linen, 1904-11-01 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - girder D (9-14) section C; ink on linen, 1904-10-31 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - bay window framing; ink on linen, 1904-11-02 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - additional framing for assembly hall platform; ink on linen, 1906-09-19 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - roof purlin plan, panels S r/l; ink on linen, 1905-03-16 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - roof purlin plan panels O, R & BB; ink on linen, 1905-04-26 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - roof purlin plan panels L, M & AA; ink on linen, 1905-03-10 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - roof purlin plan panels X, U & Y; ink on linen, 1905-05-01 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - roof purlin plan panels CC, DD & EE; ink on linen, 1905-05-05 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - purlin plan for panel E, section C; ink on linen, 1905-04-25 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - dormer D1, panel F; ink on linen, 1905-04-25 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - deck houses, N & S towers; ink on linen, 1905-05-02 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - L tier girders; ink on linen, 1905-04-19 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - details of roof houses for main tower; ink on linen, 1905-04-25 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - plate girder, apse roof; ink on linen, 1905-04-26 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - plate girders, apse roof; ink on linen, 1905-04-29 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - purlin plan for panel D; ink on linen, 1905-05-01 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - framing proscenium arch; ink on linen, 1905-09-21 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - partition lintels, sect. C; ink on linen, 1905-09-13 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - door bucks & partition lintels; ink on linen, 1905-09-13 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - bucks & lintels for section C; ink on linen, 1905-09-13 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - plain lintels, door bucks for sections AB & DE; ink on linen, 1905-09-13 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - partition lintels for sections AB & DE; ink on linen, 1905-09-13 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - girders, section C; ink on linen, 1904-11-09 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - girders, F tier 4th fl.; ink on linen, 1904-10-20 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - water tank; ink on linen (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - framing: details of columns and girders; ink on linen (33 sheets), 1904 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - truss T2, sect. C; ink on linen, 1904-12-21 (Box 372-A)
  - Main Building - framing: advance sheet, altered plan of reading room, etc.; blueprint on paper (Box 369)
  - Main Building - detail for steel framing, 3rd & 4th floor, museum, main tower; blueprint on paper, 1904-11-14 (Box 369)
  - Main Building - rafter cut & placed to escape mechanism for darkening shades, labs, 3rd fl.; blueprint on paper, 1905-10-10 (Box 369)
  - Main Building - detail of steel framing for fan room & roof, main tower; blueprint on paper (damaged, unusable), 1905-1-24 (Box OS-1)
  - Main Building - details of upper part of south tower; blueprint on paper (damaged, unusable) (Box OS-1)
  - Main Building - sections; aniline on paper, 1904-12-14 (Box OS-1)
  - Main Building - detail of large gablesadjoining wings A & E, campus elevation; aniline on paper (damaged, unusable), 1904-12-14 (Box OS-1)
  - Main Building - campus, Convent Ave. & park elevations; aniline on paper, 1904-12-14 (Box OS-1)
  - Main Building - details of upper part of north tower; aniline on linen, 1905-03-11 (Box 369)
  - Main Building - interior detail, museum, 3rd & 4th fl., main tower; aniline on paper, 1905-03-1905 (Box 369)
  - Main Building - basement plan; aniline on paper, 1904-12-14 (Box 369)
  - General plans - diagram of curved approaches; aniline on paper, 1904-03-22 (Box 369)
  - Main Building - interior details of main tower, ground fl.; aniline on paper, 1904-12-14 (Box 369)
  - Main Building - terrace elevation; aniline on paper (damaged), 1904-03-22 (Box OS-1)
  - Main Building - 1st floor plan; aniline on paper (damaged, 2 pieces), 1904-12-14 (Box 369)
  - Main Building - detail of ends of assembly hall; aniline on paper (damaged), 1904-07-20 (Box 369-A)
  - General plan - blasting plan; aniline on paper (damaged) (Box 369-A)
  - Main Building - interior details of north & south towers; aniline on paper (damaged), 1905-01-27 (Box 369-A)
  - Main Building - details of curved wings B & D; aniline on paper (damaged, 2 pieces), 1904-12-14 (Box 369-A)
  - Main Building - steel framing of 3rd & 4th fl., museum, main tower; aniline on paper (damaged, 2 pieces), 1904-12-14 (Box 369-A)
  - Main Building - framing sections & plans of tower; aniline on paper (damaged, 2 pieces) (Box 369-A)
  - Chemical Building - piping system, basement ceiling; ink on linen (Box OS-2)
  - Chemical Building - details of end wings; ink on linen, 1905-02-20 (Box OS-2)
  - Chemical Building - details of central portion campus & 140th St. elevations, 1905-02-20 (Box OS-2)
  - All buildings - plaster transom, running plaster mould above wainscoting, terra cotta tile wainscot in corridors & staircase halls etc.; graphite on trace, 1905-06-19 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - details for bronze frames & register screens in front of radiators either side of entrance doors to N & S towers; graphite on trace, 1907-01-16 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - location of cutout boxes; graphite on trace, 1905-10-27 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - location of cutout box, 3rd fl.; graphite on trace, 1905-10-27 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - location of cutout box, 2nd story; graphite on trace, 1905-10-27 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - detail of wainscot in cast room; ink on linen (Box 379)
  - Main Building - sliding roof, south tower; graphite on trace, 1906-12-11 (Box 379)
  - All buildings - toilet room slate & marble work in connection with fixtures; graphite on trace, 1905-07-14 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - detail of pilaster bases (elevation), assembly hall; graphite on trace (Box 379)
  - Main Building - partition between rooms 1 & 3, 5th floor; graphite on trace (Box 379)
  - Main Building - interior details of reading room; graphite on trace, 1905-10-10 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - details of frame for octagonal turret C-50, main tower; ink on linen, 1904-04-02 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - stack room, reading room & mezzanine floor plans, library; ink on linen (Box 379)
  - Main Building - key plan to large column bases etc., assembly hall; ink on linen, 1906-03-15 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - key plan to arch mouldings & capitals, assembly hall; ink on linen, 1906-01-05 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - location of cutout boxes, ground fl.; graphite on trace, 1905-10-12 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - walls & window openings, lower part of main tower; ink on linen (Box 379)
  - Main Building - details of door from stack room to small lavatory; graphite on trace (Box 379)
  - Main Building - detail of stepings in lecture rooms; graphite on trace, 1906-01-13 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - details for dresser in janitor's kitchen; graphite on trace, 1907-10-07 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - plan of lecture rooms; graphite on trace, 1906-04-17 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - opening btwn corridor & hat & coat room; ink on linen, 1905-03-17 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - diagram of arch; ink on linen, 1906-11-14 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - cutout box in corridor B, 3rd fl.; graphite on trace, 1906-03-09 (Box 379)
  - All buildings - plaster cornice in corridors; graphite on trace, 1905-05-31 (Box 379)
  - All buildings - marble treads and risers on staircases; graphite on trace, 1905-06-29 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - wood & glass partitions in corridors of 4th fl.; graphite on trace, 1905-11-14 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - copper cornice & gutter of deck house on main tower; graphite on trace, 1907-01-11 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - temporary partition & curtain across proscenium; graphite on trace, 1907-09-07 (Box 379)
  - Main Building - details of doors etc., exhibition hall to room [...]; graphite on trace (damaged) (Box 379-A)
  - Main Building - interior wood doors; graphite on trace (damaged) (Box 379-A)
  - Main Building - detail of special lower sashes; ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-11 (Box 379-A)
  - All buildings - elevator car grille; graphite on trace (damaged), 1905-08-09 (Box 379-A)
  - Main Building - fragment showing partitions; graphite on trace (damaged), 1906-01-05 (Box 379-A)
  - Main Building - details of trim in connection with darkening shades; blueprint on paper (damaged), 1905-01-18 (Box 379-A)
  - Main Building - details of trim in connection with darkening shades; blueprint on paper (Box 379-A)
  - All buildings - general scheme for enclosing stair case wells; blueprint on paper, 1903-11-12 (Box 379-A)
  - Main Building - new location of exhaust registers in apse platform; blueprint on paper, 1906-04-28 (Box 379-A)
  - Main Building - new location of exhaust registers in apse platform; blueprint on paper (Box 379-A)
  - Main Building - sketch showing changes to be made in setting of shields on wings A & E; blueprint on paper (Box 379-A)
  - Main Building - entrance doors at platform end of assembly hall, 2nd fl.; blueprint on paper (Box 379-A)
  - General plans - wall sections; ink on linen (damaged), 1903-01-26 (Box 378)
  - General plans - blasting plan; ink on linen (damaged), 1903-01-26 (Box 378)
  - General plans - details of approaches, Main Building; ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-01 (Box 378)
  - General plans - approaches, Main Building; ink on linen (damaged) (2 sheets), 1905-02-20 (Box 378)
  - General plans - details of subway from Main to Chemical buildings; ink on linen (damaged) (Box 378)
  - General plans - sections of subways; ink on linen (damaged), 1905-02-20 (Box 378)
  - General plans - details of subway from Chemical Bldg. to 139th St.; ink on linen (damaged), 1905-02-20 (Box 378)
  - General plans - details of subway from 139th St. to Gymnasium; ink on linen (damaged), 1904-11-01 (Box 378)
  - All buildings - arrangement of nos. for lockers; graphite on trace (damaged)
  - General plans - details for anchoring lamp posts; ink on linen (damaged), 1905-06-01 (Box 387)
  - General plans - details for anchoring lamp posts; ink on linen (damaged), 1905-08-30 (Box 378)
  - General plans - fuse switch in base of lamp post; ink on linen (damaged), 1907-05-27 (Box 378)
  - General plans - section thro' parapet wall above subway, anchorage for lamp posts; ink on linen (damaged), 1905-02-09 (Box 378)
  - General plans - table on granite coping of subway to receive lamp stands; graphite on trace (damaged), 1906-03-23 (Box 378)
  - General plans - stand for laying of corner stone; graphite on trace (damaged) (Box 378)
  - General plans - details for general plan no. 3; ink on linen (damaged) (Box 378)
  - General plans - windows in subway walls over pipe gallery; ink on linen (damaged) (Box 378)
  - General plans - granite coping on parapet walls of subway; graphite on trace (damaged), 1906-01-05 (Box 378)
  - General plans - diagram of curved approaches; ink on linen (damaged) (Box 378)
  - General plans - details of approaches, Main Building; aniline on linen, 1905-10-25 (Box 380)
  - General plans - approaches, Main Building; aniline on linen, 1905-10-25 (Box 380)
  - General plans - location of subways; blueprint on paper, 1904-10-21 (Box 380)
  - Main Building - detail of dark room partitions; graphite on trace (damaged), 1906-01-10 (Box 380)
  - Main Building - detail of cast iron door frames & partitions; graphite on trace (damaged), 1905-09-20 (Box 380)
  - Main Building - iron bucks & lintels for interior doors, etc; graphite on trace (damaged), 1905-06-16 (Box 380)
  - Main Building - iron frames, doors, etc. for elevator; graphite on trace (damaged), 1905-09-28 (Box 380)